What is this, a dream?
That's right, a dream.
Of course it's a dream.
A bad dream, just a bad dream!
The worst part about dreaming is the moment you wake up.
It's supposed to be that way.
Open your eyes, don't do anything and settle down.
Nothing will change. It's just a normal room.
Calm down, this is just a dream!
Huh, a dream?
Yes.
What am I doing?
A normal morning.
Nothing different from yesterday.
Was the sheep doll, the star drops and everything just a dream?
Yo, Haru.
Morning!
Then why was I sleeping in Akihime's room?
You never change, Tsuwabuki.
Hey, Haru. I heard you joined the Gardening Club. Is that true?
Huh? Kinda.
I never knew you liked gardening...
Well, that's...
Ah, Nako-san.
Good morning, Sumomo-chan.
Morning.
Morning...
I wonder why Akihime is different at school.
Well it's fine since I returned to my old self.
Eh? Uwahhh!
G-Guess it's going to be like this...
Yep, that's how it's going to be indeed.
In the morning as the sun comes up, you go back to your human body.
When the day is over, you will be back to your doll body.
It's an easy rule to understand.
So it's like that...
That, and the transformation effect in Figurare has a connection with the moon phase.
The moon phase?
For example during the new moon, you will not transform.
You will stay your human form for the whole day.
But watch out, during the opposite phase, full moon, you will stay as a doll the whole day.
Why?!
Like I said, it's the moon effect.
Well then, Tsuwabuki-kun.
Tonight you will go to the Stellar Spinear's side again.
By the way, one more thing...
Don't let anyone see you taking the star drops, okay?!
Otherwise, it will become really complicated.
I'm flying...
Alright!
Err...
Uwahh, it's so cute!
It just came in today.
This is a uniform I made a long time ago.
Now Sumomo, I think it will fit you perfectly.
It will look nice on you.
From... Mother.
Even though she's overseas, Mom always thinks of you everyday, Sumomo.
Thank you, Mom.
Well then, I'll go finish writing my manuscript.
Deadlines, deadlines...
Okay.
So Akihime's father is a novel writer?
And her mother is overseas.
Yuki-chan.
Where did you go? You were gone this morning.
I thought Yuki-chan and the star drops were just a dream.
I can't breathe...
It seems that I can only come here during the night.
I see.
Also, we shouldn't let anyone see us when we're using magic.
Okay! Then...
Cute!
You look so cute, Yuki-chan.
Looking good! All of them look lovely.
As I thought, compared to her at school, she looks more lively at home.
Yep, let's use this one.
Am I a cow now?
It's here!
It's the star drop.
Where is it?
The ring isn't responding anymore.
It's there!
I can't reach it.
A little bit more. Go for it!
The star drops have an affinity to water, so...
it must be chasing the rain.
Aki- Sumomo!
Yuki-chan.
You're using my name.
Are you okay? You look really wet too.
Are you alright, Sumomo?
N-Nako-chan.
Sumomo!
Nako-chan, watch out!
For real?!
Sumomo, use the chant.
Puruvu Radi!
I-I got it!
I got it! Yuki-chan, I got it, the star drop!
Oh noooo!
Someone saw us!
Sumomo, why don't you come by my house?
You'll catch a cold with those wet clothes.
Okay?
Yaeno...
Shall I clean your butt too?
No thanks!
That was you speaking, right?
Yes.
I see, so you can speak.
I saw you moving and jumping around too.
S-She saw everything!
Nako-chan, that was a good bath.
Do you feel better now?
Yes.
Did you clean those?
What is this thing called?
Sorry, she found out.
Err, umm... I'm sorry, it's not that I wanted to hide Yuki-chan from you.
So it's called Yuki-chan.
It's already late now so shall we head out?
Mom said she will drive you back home.
Found it. Here it is.
When a person from Retroscena sees a Spinear gathering star drops,
that person's memory must be deleted.
By using the Ladle to hit the person's head,
the memory can be erased using the power from Figurare.
Delete the memory...?
Looks like we are okay...
I can't do it; such a thing as deleting Nako-chan's memories...
But you will only delete the memory about the incident.
I can't do it...
It's not like Nako-chan is going to forget about you...
But the memory of Nako-chan cleaning these clothes will disappear...
Nako-chan cleaned it carefully from top to bottom.
Deleting such a kind feeling from her...
I can't do it...
We've always been together...
Since we were little.
Nako-chan was always there for me.
Always taking care of me.
Sumomo...
But I...
I can't do it.
Sumomo...
With the Gardening Club privilege, I'm going to take a Hydrangea flower.
Okay.
Sumomo?
Eh?
Things seem awkward between them.
Must be because of what happened yesterday.
I have a favor to ask you.
Can you walk Sumomo home today?
Huh?
Me with Akihime?
How about you, Nako-chan?
I have to stop by somewhere to take care of something for my mother.
Don't push yourself like yesterday, okay?
Or you'll catch a cold.
Tsuwabuki, I'm counting on you.
Okay.
It's raining.
I-I'm sorry.
Umm...
Y-Yes?
Just talk normally.
Just a normal answer is fine.
Yes!
Are you alright?
Since you are different than usual, Akihime.
What happened?
Do you have a special friend, Tsuwabuki-kun?
Someone that you've been with since you were young.
And you talk about everything with her.
Keeping no secrets.
A really important friend.
Umm...
Continue on with the story.
With such an important friend like that,
you shouldn't lie or something like that, right?
You can, maybe...
Eh?
Because lies come in different types.
You treasure your friend very much, right?
Then I think everything is fine.
Sorry, I can't say it any better.
Escorting you this far is fine, right?
I have to get back now.
Later.
Tsuwabuki-kun...
This is strange, I'm not transforming.
The sun should have gone down already.
Tonight is...?
During the new moon, you will not transform.
You will stay your human form the whole day.
New moon...
Kisaragi-sensei!
Of course, he is not here anymore.
Is there any other way without erasing Yaeno's memory?
I'm thinking Sensei might have an idea.
Damn it! What can I do?!
Ah, I see!
Sumomo-chan, you got a letter.
I'm sorry, tonight I cannot go to Sumomo's place.
But I found this in the book.
A way so that we don't have to erase Nako-chan's memory.
If you two truly believe in each other then telling the secret is permitted.
To only one person.
Listen, chant this while holding Nako-chan's hand.
Ruaro
If Sumomo-chan and Nako-chan truly believe in each other then...
...a mark will appear.
On the next day I found it.
The mark of a believer.
I wonder why I feel so surprisingly relieved.
During Tanabata...
Why does it rain every year?
Even when it's a day for lovers.
That's why it rains.
What?!
Speaking of which, on Tanabata a transfer student came.
What kind of person?
Beautiful girl?
Beautiful girl.
Love at first sight with me!
That...
won't happen.